Ojora Oyeyinka Olamide



oyeyinkaojora@yahoo.com



08121841772



linkedin.com/in/ojora-oyeyinka-olamide-5b8568169

https://github.com/oyeyinkaojora

Summary

I'm a Front End Developer(Reactjs) with 8 months of Industrial Experience, I enjoy developing friendly UI and also the integration of the backend API,I keep learning every day in other to up my skills, and I'll be a great asset to any company that employs me because I have learned a lot and that means I have a lot to offer the company that employs me and I can also learn on the job, Plus I'm smart and intelligent.

Experience



Frontend Developer

mycroft

Mar 2022 - Present (4 months +)

Working with the lead frontend engineer to build a scalable design and architecture

Software Devlopement Training

Alabian Solutions Limited Jun 2018 - Aug 2018 (3 months)

Education



🌉 Lagos State University

Bachelor of Science - BS (2:1), Physics and electronics 2017 - Jun 2022

Licenses & Certifications



Responsive Web Design - freeCodeCamp

Skills

Tailwind CSS • Problem Solving • React.js • Programming Languages • GitHub • Git • JavaScript